Guide to the Arthur Einstein Papers, 1978-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Arthur Einstein papers 1978-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Einstein, Arthur W.
54.0 linear feet Extent: 30,000 Items
Advertising executive for Lord Geller Federico Einstein, Lord Einstein O'Neill; Arthur Einstein Advertising, an advertising and consulting firm; and Loyalty Builders LLC, a marketing services company. Collection spans the years 1978-2001 and includes advertising agency credentials presentations, correspondence, print advertisements, audiocassettes, videocassettes, compact discs, 16mm films, clippings and other materials that document Arthur Einstein's career as an advertising executive and consultant. Companies represented include Bankers Trust, Compaq, DDB Needham, Foote Cone Belding, IBM, the New York Stock Exchange, Oppenheimer Funds, Saab and Steinway. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.10039
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Arthur Einstein Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1993-2002.
Biographical Note
Arthur W. Einstein, Jr. was born in 1933. He received a BS from the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill and an MS in Communications from Michigan State University. He began work at Lord Southard Federico (later Lord Geller Federico) and rose to become partner in that firm prior to its acquisition by J. Walter Thompson (JWT). Einstein founded his own agency, Arthur Einstein Advertising and in 2013 was a consultant and Vice President of Loyalty Builders LLC.
Collection Overview
Collection spans the years 1978-2001 and includes advertising agency credentials presentations, correspondence, print advertisements, audiocassettes, videocassettes, compact discs, 16mm films, clippings and other materials that document Arthur Einstein's career as an advertising executive and consultant. Companies represented include Bankers Trust, Compaq, DDB Needham, Foote Cone Belding, IBM, the New York Stock Exchange, Oppenheimer Funds, Saab and Steinway.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged into six series: Agency Search Files; General Agency Files; Lord Einstein O'Neill; Lord Geller Federico Einstein; Oversize Materials; and Audiovisual Materials.
Subject Headings
Einstein, Arthur W., 1933-; Bankers Trust Company (New York, N.Y.); Compaq Computer Corporation; DDB Needham Worldwide; Foote, Cone & Belding; International Business Machines Corporation; New York Stock Exchange; Oppenheimer Funds; Saab (Firm); Steinway & Sons; Advertising; Advertising -- United States; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising executives; Advertising executives -- United States; Consulting firms; Consulting firms -- United States; Audiocassettes; Compact discs; Videocassettes; 16mm; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Alvin A. Achenbaum Papers
Bates Worldwide Inc. Records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Advertising Vertical Files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements
J. Walter Thompson Company. New Business Records
Robert S. Smith Papers
Stephen Harty Papers
Wunderman Archives
Detailed Description of Collection
- Agency Search Files, 1991-2000 and undated, (13 boxes)
  Includes agency credentials, correspondence, summary reports and other materials documenting Einstein's consulting activities for named and unnamed clients.
  - Bankers Trust
    - Agency review, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
    - Agency search second round, undated (Box 1)
    - Chase GFS (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 1)
    - Chermayeff & Geismar (N.Y.), trademarks, undated (Box 1)
    - Citigate Albert Frank (N.Y.), undated (Box 1)
    - Cox & Marshall (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 1)
    - Cox Group (N.Y.), 1995, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Diversified Agency Services (DAS, N.Y.)/Omnicom, undated (Box 1)
    - Earle Palmer Brown (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 1)
    - Fallon McElligott Berlin (Minn.), 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - FGI Integrated Marketing (N.Y.), undated (Box 1)
    - Graf Bertel Buczek (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 1)
    - Jerry & Ketchum (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 2)
    - Margeotes Fertitta (N.Y.), 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Marshall Jaccoma Mitchell (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 2)
    - McKinney & Silver (N.C.), 1995 (Box 2)
    - Mintz & Hoke (Conn.), 1995 (Box 2)
    - Porter Novelli (N.Y.), undated (Box 2)
    - Siegel & Gale (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 2)
    - Slater Hanft Martin (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 2)
    - Warwick Baker Fiore (N.Y.), undated (Box 2)
  - Business-to-Business Services Client
    - Anderson & Lembke (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - Angotti Thomas Hedge (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - Bates USA (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - Citigate (Calif.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - DDB Needham (Tex.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - Doremus (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - Gardner Geary Coll & Young (GGC&Y--Calif.), 1998 (Box 2)
    - Grace & Rothschild (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 3)
    - Hill Holliday (Mass.), 1998 (Box 3)
    - Margeotes Fertitta (N.Y.), undated (Box 3)
    - TBWA/Chiat/Day (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 3)
    - Temerlin McClain (Tex.), 1998 (Box 3)
    - Wieden & Kennedy (Ore.), 1998 (Box 3)
  - Canon
    - Goldsmith/Jeffrey (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 3)
  - Compaq
    - Ammirati & Puris (N.Y.), 1991 (Box 3)
    - Backer Spielvogel Bates (N.Y.), 1991 (Box 3)
    - Bozell Dallas (Tex.), 1991 (Box 3)
    - GSD&M (Tex.), undated (Box 3)
    - Hal Riney (Calif.), 1991, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - McCaffrey & McCall (N.Y.), 1991, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 3)
    - McCaffrey & McCall (N.Y.), 1991, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Messner Vetere Berger Carey Schmetterer (N.Y.), 1991 (Box 4)
    - Morgan Anderson, evaluation of agency finalists, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Ogilvy & Mather (N.Y.), 1991 (Box 4)
    - Richards Group (Tex.), 1991 (Box 4)
    - Tracy-Locke (Tex.), 1991 (Box 4)
  - Chanel
    - Agency search, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Holland Advertising (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 4)
  - IBM
    - Agency meetings, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Agency presentation schedule, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Agency review schedule, 1993, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Agency review schedule, 1993, (3 of 3 folders) (Box 5)
    - Ally & Gargano (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 5)
    - Assignment, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Backer Spielvogel Bates (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 5)
    - BDDP (France), 1993 (Box 5)
    - Charron Schwartz & Partners (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 5)
    - Chiat/Day (Mo.), 1993-1997 (Box 5)
    - Cliff Freeman & Partners (Mass.), 1993 (Box 5)
    - Communications plans and strategy, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence to Ray Freeman (IBM), 1993 (Box 5)
    - Deutsch/Dworin (N.Y.), 1993, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Don Coleman & Associates (African-American--Mich.), 1994 (Box 5)
    - DRK (Mass.), 1993, (3 folders) (Box 6)
    - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1993, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Floathe Johnson (Wash.), 1993 (Box 6)
    - Gallaspy & Lobel (Fla.), 1993, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - GGK/GGT (Ga.), 1993, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Gigante Vaz & Partners (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 6)
    - Goodby Berlin & Silverstein (Calif.), 1993 (Box 6)
    - Grey Advertising (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 6)
    - Hal Riney (Calif.), 1993 (Box 6)
    - Houston Effler Hampel & Stefanides (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 6)
    - J. Walter Thompson (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Jack Lawlor Advertising (Calif.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Jordan McGrath Case & Taylor (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - King-Casey (Conn.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Kirshenbaum & Bond (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Leo Burnett (Ill.), 1993, (4 folders) (Box 7)
    - Lord Dentsu & Partners (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Lowe & Partners (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Margeotes Fertitta & Weiss (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Merkley Newman Harty (N.Y.), 1993, (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Messner Vetere Berger McNamee Schmetterer (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Press coverage, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Rosenfeld Sirowitz Humphrey & Strauss (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Scali McCabe Sloves (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Suissa Miller (Calif.), 1993 (Box 7)
    - Top 5 agency information, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Ventre Advertising (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 8)
    - Waring & LaRosa (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 8)
    - W.B. Doner (Mich.), 1993, (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - NationsBank Montgomery
    - Agency selection binder, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Temerlin McClain (Tex.), undated (Box 8)
      [Includes American Airlines, NationsBank creative examples]
  - New York Stock Exchange
    - Agency search, candidate creative examples, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Ammirati & Puris/Lintas (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report (NYSE), 1994 (Box 8)
    - Argentina research report, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Arthur Einstein consultant agreement, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Assignment, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Bozell (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 8)
    - Communications plan, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Contracts, 1991-1993 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1994-1995, (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Creative review, 1995 (Box 9)
    - DDB Needham (N.Y.), 1995-1996, (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Exchange Magazine, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Fact Book, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1995 (Box 9)
    - Goodby Silverstein (Calif.), 1995 (Box 9)
    - Hazel Kahan (N.Y.) opinion research, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
    - KRC Research and Consulting (N.Y.), evaluation of NYSE communications, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Leo Burnett (Ill.), 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Lunch meeting, Sao Paolo, Brazil, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Margeotes Fertitta (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 9)
    - NASDAQ advertising, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Nightly Business Report, 1995 June 2 (Box 10)
    - Wells Rich Greene (N.Y.), 1991-1996, (8 folders) (Box 10)
  - Oppenheimer Funds
    - Adler Boschetto Peebles (N.Y.), 1996, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Agency search, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Amil Gargano & Partners (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 10)
    - Anderson & Lembke (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Angotti Thomas Hedge (N.Y.), 1996, (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - Assignment, undated (Box 11)
    - Barry & Blau (Conn.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Bruoillard Communications (N.Y.), 1996, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMBB) (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - DDB Needham (N.Y.), undated (Box 11)
    - Deutsch/Dworin (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Doremus (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Dweck & Campbell (N.Y.), undated (Box 11)
    - Emmerling Post (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Frank Luca & Partners (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Glennon Company (Mo.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Kirshenbaum Bond & Partners (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Korey Kay & Partners (N.Y.), 1996, (2 folders) (Box 11)
      [Includes report Outsmarting the Outspenders]
    - Leibler-Bronfman Lubalin (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - Lord Dentsu & Partners (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - Marsteller Advertising (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - McKinney & Silver (N.C.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - Messner Vetere Berger McNamee Schmetterer (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - MgM & Partners (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - Muldoon Agency (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - New York Creatives (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - Oasis (N.Y.), undated (Box 12)
    - Partners & Shevack (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 12)
    - Public Sector Solutions (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 13)
    - Trone Advertising (N.C.), 1996 (Box 13)
    - Weinstein Otterman (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 13)
    - Wells Rich Greene (N.Y.), 1996, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Woman's Guide to Investing (direct mail booklet from Oppenheimer), 1997 (Box 13)
  - Thomas Weisel Partners
    - Agency Selection, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Arnold Ingalls Moranville (Calif.), 2000 (Box 13)
    - Butler Shine & Stern (Calif.), 2000 (Box 13)
    - Citron Haligman Bedecarré (Calif.), undated (Box 13)
    - Compensation proposals, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Connected Brands (Calif.), undated (Box 13)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Hill Holliday (Calif.), 2000 (Box 13)
    - Thomas Weisel Partners business overview, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Thomas Weisel Partners corporate brand guidelines, undated (Box 13)
- General Agency File, 1989-2001 and undated, (19 boxes)
  Primarily correspondence and agency credentials reports and presentations sent to Einstein by prospective agencies and maintained as a vertical file. Where known, the state or country of the agency's home office is indicated.
  - Abbott Mead Vickers (Great Britain), 1996 (Box 14)
  - Abramson Ehrlich Manes (D.C.), 1996 (Box 14)
  - Accent Marketing (Hispanic--Fla.), 1998 (Box 14)
  - ACE Group (N.Y.), undated (Box 14)
  - Adamson (Mo.), 1998 (Box 14)
  - AdAnswers (Mo.), 1997 (Box 14)
  - ADM Productions (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 14)
  - AdMedia Partners (N.Y.), 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - Air Creative Group (Calif.), 1997 (Box 14)
  - Alden Group (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 14)
  - Allen & Gerritsen (Mass.), 1997 (Box 14)
  - Ally & Gargano (N.Y.), circa 1993 (Box 14)
  - Al Paul Lefton Company (Pa.), 1997 (Box 14)
  - Ames Scullin O'Haire (Ga.), 1997 (Box 14)
  - Ammirati & Puris/Lintas (N.Y.), 1994-1999 (Box 14)
  - Amster-Young Public Relations (AYPR--N.Y.), 1999 (Box 14)
  - Anderson & Lembke (N.Y.), 1993-1997, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Anderson Partners (Neb.), 1997-1999 (Box 14)
  - Angotti Thomas Hedge (N.Y.), 1994-1996, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Arian Lowe & Travis (Ill.), 1997, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Arnold Communications (Mass.), 2000 (Box 15)
  - Artustry Partnership (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 15)
  - Asher & Partners (Calif.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Asher/Gould (Calif.), 1997 (Box 15)
  - Aslan Group (Ga.), 1996 (Box 15)
    [Includes Proven Strategies for Business Success by Os Hillman]
  - Austin Kelley Advertising (Ga.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Bader Rutter & Associates (Wis.), 1997 (Box 15)
  - Bailey Group (Calif.), 1994 (Box 15)
  - Bailey Lauerman & Associates (Neb.), 1996 (Box 15)
  - Balet & Albert (N.Y.), 1994-1996 (Box 15)
  - Bandy Carroll Hellige (Ky.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Barber Martin & Associates (Va.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Barkley Evergreen & Partners (Mo.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Bartle Bogle Hegarty (Great Britain), 1993 (Box 15)
  - Bates USA (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 15)
  - Bawden & Associates (Ia.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Bayer Brown Advertising (Nev.), 1995 (Box 15)
  - BBDO (N.Y.), 1994 (Box 15)
  - BDDP (France), 1993 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Bender Browning Dolby & Sanderson (BBD&S--Wis.), 1996 (Box 15)
  - Berenter Greenhouse & Webster (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 15)
  - Bernstein-Rein (Mo.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Berry Brown (Tex.), 2000 (Box 15)
  - BGM Health Communications (Calif.), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Bileteki Armoni (Israel), 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - BJK&E [Bozell Jacobs Kenyon and Eckhardt] Media Group (N.Y.), undated (Box 16)
  - Blanc & Otus (Calif.), 1994 (Box 16)
  - Bleeker & Sullivan (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 16)
  - Bloom FCA! (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 16)
  - Bohan Carden & Cherry (Tenn.), 2000 (Box 16)
  - Borders Perrin & Norrander (BP&E--Ore.), 1994 (Box 16)
  - Bozell (N.Y.), 1994-1998 (Box 16)
  - Broadwell Marketing (Tex.), 1998 (Box 16)
  - Brodeur & Partners (Calif.), 1994 (Box 16)
  - Brooks Communication Design (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 16)
  - Brouillard Communications (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 16)
  - Butler Shine & Stern (Calif.), 1994 (Box 16)
  - Campbell-Ewald (Mich.), 1999 (Box 16)
  - Campbell Group (Md.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - Campbell Mithun Esty (Minn.), 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - Carat North America (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - Carmichael Lynch (Minn.), 1998 (Box 17)
  - Castle Underwood (N.Y.), 1994-1995 (Box 17)
  - Creative Consortium International (CCI--N.Y.), 1996 (Box 17)
  - CCM (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 17)
  - Center for Communications (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 17)
  - Charron Schwartz & Partners (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - Chicago Creative Partnership (Ill.), 1998 (Box 17)
  - Chinnici Direct (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - Ciociola & Company (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - Citigate Albert Frank (Calif.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - Clarion Marketing & Communications (Conn.), 1998 (Box 17)
    [Disc contents migrated to server. Consult Reference staff for assistance.]
  - Clarity Coverdale Fury (Minn.), 1998 (Box 17)
  - Cliff Freeman & Partners (N. Y.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - CMG Communications (N.Y.), 1996-1997 (Box 17)
  - Cole Henderson Drake (Ga.), 1997 (Box 17)
  - Citron Haligman Bedecarré (Calif.), 1993 (Box 18)
  - Colle & McVoy (Minn.), 1997-1999 (Box 18)
  - Connors Communications (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 18)
  - Corinthian Media (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 18)
  - Cowles Magazines (N.Y.), undated (Box 18)
  - Cox Group (N.Y.), 1993-1998 (Box 18)
  - CPS Group (Tex.), 1998 (Box 18)
  - Cramer-Krasselt (Wis.), 1997-1998 (Box 18)
  - Cranford Johnson Robinson Woods (CJRW--Ark.), 1995-1998 (Box 18)
  - Creative Media (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 18)
  - Credit Suisse/First Boston (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 18)
    [English and German]
  - Crispin Porter Bogusky (Fla.), 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - Cronin & Company (Conn.), 1996 (Box 18)
  - Cross Creative Resources (N.M.), 1996 (Box 18)
  - Christopher Thomas Associates (Mass.), 1998 (Box 18)
  - Cullinan Group (Minn.), undated (Box 18)
  - Cuneo Sullivan Dolabany (Mass.), 1996 (Box 18)
  - Cunningham Communications (Calif.), 1994 (Box 18)
  - Curvin O'Reilly (N.Y.), 1994 (Box 18)
  - D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMBB) (N.Y.), 1994-1998 (Box 18)
  - DDB Needham (N.Y.), 1993-1998, (3 folders) (Box 19)
  - Deutsch/Dworin (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 19)
  - DeVito Fitterman (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 19)
  - Dialogue Works (N.Y.), undated (Box 19)
  - DiMark (Pa.), 1998 (Box 19)
  - DiMassimo (N.Y.), 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - DiMeo & Co. (Ill.), 1998 (Box 19)
  - DMW Worldwide (Pa.), 1999 (Box 19)
  - Doe-Anderson (Ky.), 1998 (Box 19)
  - Don Coleman & Associates (African-American--Mich.), 1994 (Box 19)
  - Doremus (N.Y.), 1997-1999 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Douglas-Danielle (Ill.), 1998 (Box 19)
  - Doyle Inc. (Mass.), 1994 (Box 19)
  - Draft Direct (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 19)
  - Duffy Design (N.Y.), undated (Box 19)
  - Dweck & Campbell (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 20)
  - Earle Palmer Brown (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 20)
  - Edelman (Calif.), 1995 (Box 20)
  - Edelman Scott (Va.), undated (Box 20)
  - ELAN (European Local Agency Network--France), 1994-1995 (Box 20)
  - Elberson Senger Shuller (N.C.), 1996-1998 (Box 20)
  - Emmerling Post (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 20)
  - Enterprise Creative Selling (Canada), 1998 (Box 20)
  - Eons Ahead (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 20)
  - Eric Mower & Associates (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 20)
  - Euro RSCG (N.Y.), 2001 (Box 20)
  - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1998 (Box 20)
  - Ferrell Calvillo (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 20)
  - FGI (N.C.), 1995 (Box 20)
  - Fitch (Mich.), 1998 (Box 20)
  - Fitzgerald & Company (Ga.), 1995 (Box 20)
  - Fletcher Martin Associates/Fletcher Martin & Ewing (Ga.), 1999 (Box 20)
  - Focus Agency (Tex.), 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Follis Advertising (N.Y.), 1986-1996 (Box 20)
  - Foote Cone Belding (Calif.), 1993-1996, (3 folders) (Box 21)
    [Includes True North Communications]
  - Frankel & Company (Ill.), 1996 (Box 21)
  - Fred Riger (N.Y.), 1999 (Box 21)
  - Fricks Advertising (Ga.), 1996 (Box 21)
  - Friedman & Rose (Mass.), 1996 (Box 21)
  - Furman Communications/Luxury Marketing Council (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 21)
  - Furman Roth (Radio advertising--N.Y.), 1996 (Box 21)
  - Gardner Geary Coll & Young (GGC&Y--Calif.), 1997 (Box 21)
  - Genova Hartwick Juliano (Conn.), 1995 (Box 21)
  - Gerald Siegel & Associates (Ill.), 1996 (Box 21)
  - Gigante Vaz & Partners (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 21)
  - Gillespie (N.J.), 1994-1997 (Box 21)
  - Gillespie/Zoot Suit (Children's marketing--N.J.), 1997 (Box 21)
  - Gillis (Ala.), 1997 (Box 21)
  - Gleason Calise Associates (GCA--Tex.), 1997 (Box 21)
  - Glennon Company (Mo.), 1996 (Box 21)
  - Goldsmith/Jeffrey (N.Y.), 1996, (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - Grant/Jacoby (Ill.), 1997 (Box 21)
  - Gray Kirk/VanSant (Md.), 1995 (Box 21)
  - Greenstone Roberts (Fla.), 1994 (Box 21)
  - Grey Advertising (N.Y.), 1992 (Box 21)
  - Ground Zero (Calif.), 1994 (Box 21)
  - Grybauskas Beatrice (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 21)
  - GSD&M (Tex.), 1994 (Box 21)
  - Hadeler Sullivan & Law (Tex.) (Box 22)
  - Hal Riney (Calif.), 1993 (Box 22)
    [Saturn creative]
  - Harpell/Martins (Mass.), 1998 (Box 22)
  - Harris Drury Cohen (Fla.), 1997-1999 (Box 22)
  - Hawk Media (Calif.), 1999 (Box 22)
  - Heinrich Marketing/Heinrich Integrated Response (Colo.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Hensley Segal Rentschler (Oh.), 1998 (Box 22)
  - Herring/Newman (Wash.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Hi-Tech Communications (Calif.), 1993 (Box 22)
  - Hill Holliday (Mass.), 1997-1998 (Box 22)
  - Hitchcock Fleming & Associates (Oh.), 1996-1999 (Box 22)
  - HMS Partners (Oh.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Howard Merrell & Partners (N.C.), 1996-1998 (Box 22)
  - Hughes Advertising (Ga.), 1997-1998 (Box 22)
  - Ichat (Tex.), 1996 (Box 22)
  - ICOM (International Communications Agency Network--Colo.), 1998 (Box 22)
  - Images USA (Ga.), 1998 (Box 22)
  - James Bunting Advertising (Pa.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Jamison Cawdrey Advertising (Calif.), undated (Box 22)
    [Insighter newsletter]
  - Joe & Sam Advertising (N.Y.), undated (Box 22)
  - Johnson Direct Advertising (Calif.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Jordan Tampaz Caruso (Ill.), 1997 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Just Partners (Va.), 1998 (Box 22)
  - JWT (J. Walter Thompson-- N.Y.), 1994 (Box 22)
    [Includes JWTrends, Marketing in Crisis]
  - K2 Design (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Kaplan Thaler Group (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Kasindorf & Sullivan (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 22)
  - Katz Dochtermann & Epstein (KD&E--N.Y.), 1992-1995 (Box 22)
  - Kerker & Associates (Minn.), 1995-1997 (Box 22)
  - Keyes Martin (N.J.), 1997 (Box 22)
  - Korey Kay & Partners (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 23)
  - Krimstein/Clapps (N.Y.), 1994 (Box 23)
  - KSK Communications (Va.), 1995 (Box 23)
  - Kuhlmann Lutz & Brown (Tex.), 1997 (Box 23)
  - Lassalle O'Brien (Md.), 1995 (Box 23)
  - Leap Partnership (Calif.), 1997 (Box 23)
  - Leonard Monahan Lubars & Partners (R.I.), undated (Box 23)
  - Letvin DiCicco & Battista (Pa.), 1996-1997 (Box 23)
  - LevLane (LVL) Advertising (Pa.), 1997-1998 (Box 23)
  - Liggett-Stashower (Oh.), 1997-1998 (Box 23)
  - Litzky Moore Associates (N.J.), 1992 (Box 23)
  - List/Morgan Shorey (Ga.), 1998 (Box 23)
  - Loeffler Ketchum Mountjoy (N.C.), 1995-1996 (Box 23)
  - Lord Group (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 23)
  - Lotas Minard Patton MacIver (Advertising to women--N.Y.), 1997 (Box 23)
  - Louis Harris & Associates (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 23)
  - Lowe Direct/Lowe & Partners (N.Y.), 1993 and undated (Box 23)
  - Lowe Group (Great Britain). undated (Box 23)
  - Lunt Sausville Burek (N.Y.), 1997-1998 (Box 23)
  - Mackenzie River Co. (Ore.), 1993 (Box 23)
  - Mad Dogs and Englishmen (N.Y.), undated (Box 23)
  - MARC Advertising (Pa.), 1998-1999 (Box 23)
  - Margeotes Fertitta & Partners (N.Y.), 1989-1998 (Box 24)
  - Marquardt & Roche/Meditz & Hackett (Conn.), 1997 (Box 24)
  - Marshall Jaccoma Mitchell (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 24)
  - Martin Agency (Va.), 1996-1997 (Box 24)
  - Martin/Williams (Minn.), 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box 24)
    [Includes Target case study]
  - Maslow Lumia Bartorillo (Pa.), 1996 (Box 24)
  - Masterson Rothberg (N.Y.), 1993 (Box 24)